Guide to the Nasri Fuleihan Collection AD.MC.056
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Nasri Fuleihan Collection
  - Construction of the Washington Boulevard Bridge with the Ogilvie Transportation Center in the background, Chicago., Circa 1913; ref22; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Bridges; Construction; Transportation; Buildings; Clocks/Watches; Water; Workers; English Writing; Machines; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Chicago, USA
  - A metal bridge over a river., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref23; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11.7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Rivers; Water; Bridges; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America; Buildings
  - A sitting area near a stream., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref24; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 13.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Water; Forest/Woodlands; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Furnishings; Gardens; Countryside/Rural; Mountains/Hills
  - Men walking around a dam structure., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref25; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 12 X 9.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Dams/Barrages; Men; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Water; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; North America
  - A landscape image of a bridge over a body of water., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref26; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Water; Bridges; Forest/Woodlands; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; North America; Landscapes
  - A group portrait of three women and two men., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref27; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Bags/Purses; Jewelry; Hats; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Group Portraits; North America
  - A stream in a gorge., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref28; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 13 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Water; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes
  - Group portrait of ten men., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref29; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Regional/National Dress; Swords/Knives; Weapons; Facial Hair; Palestine
  - Three men standing in front of Colonnade of Herod, Samaria., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref30; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Streets/Roads; Horses; Animals; Samaria/as-Sāmirah; English Writing; Palestine; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - Six women by a stone building in Ramallah., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref31; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Workers; Ramallah; Women; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Palestine
  - Nasri Fuleihan posing outdoors with a gun with a man in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref32; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11. 5 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Group Portraits; Hats; Cigarettes; Smoking; Weapons; Guns; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - Nasri Fuleihan (left) and a man posing holding guns with men working in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref33; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 13 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Guns; Weapons; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Deserts; Palestine
  - Nasri Fuleihan (left) posing with a man in front of rock formations., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref34; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.9 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Group Portraits; Men; Hats; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - A view of land surrounding a village., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref35; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Countryside/Rural; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - Nasri Fuleihan (left) posing with five men on the rooftop of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref36; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Group Portraits; Smoking; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Bow Ties; Tobacco pipes; Jerusalem; Outdoors; Hotels
  - Nasri Fuleihan (foreground) sitting on the ground with two men., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref37; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 12.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Group Portraits; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Outdoors; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - The interior of Masada Fortress, Judaean Desert., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref38; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 15 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Forts/Castles; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Deserts; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Judaean Desert/Sahara Yahudan; Masada; Palestine
  - Four men posing by a rock formation on Mount Sodom (Jebel Usdum), Judaean Desert., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref39; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.6 X 7.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Deserts; English Writing; Mount Sodom/Jebel Usdum, Newe Zohar; Palestine
  - Wall carvings in Caves of Maresha and Bet-Guvrin in the Judean Lowlands. Captioned: N. N. E. of Nakh Shar near Beyeviat? Wadi el Sur., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref40; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 15 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Bayt Jibrin (Beit Guvrin); Palestine; Caves; Photographic Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing
  - A silhouette of Mr. Rapps sitting in an entrance to a cave in Jebel Usdum (Mount Sodom), Judaean desert., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref41; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    English Writing; Caves; Men; Hats; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Deserts; Mount Sodom/Jebel Usdum, Newe Zohar; Judaean Desert/Sahara Yahudan; Palestine; Individual Portraits
  - A vertical view from the bottom of Wadi al Mujib, Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref42; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.5 x 8.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Ma'in, Jordan
  - Nasri Fuleihan in a car in front of the Church of Nativity, Bethlehem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref43; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.5 x 17.7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Churches; Church of the Nativity; Bethlehem; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Religious Sites; Hats; Palestine
  - A portrait of Nasri Fuleihan (left) and a man holding guns., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref44; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 13.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Group Portraits; Guns; Weapons; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Deserts; Palestine; Regional/National Dress
  - A canal lock from above., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref45; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 9.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Canals; Water; Palestine
  - A stone structure surrounded by fields., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref46; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 11.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Forest/Woodlands; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes
  - A group portrait of Nasri Fuleihan (second from the right) with three men., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref47; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 13.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Hats; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Deserts; Tents; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A sitting area surrounded by trees., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref48; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8 x 11.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Water; Forest/Woodlands; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes
  - A group portrait of Mostafa with three men., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref49; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 13.7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Regional/National Dress; Hats; Group Portraits; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; English Writing; Palestine
  - Class portraits of 1912 engineering graduates from Purdue University., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref49b; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.8 X 6.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Individual Portraits; English Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Universities; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Indiana, USA
  - A landscape of a desert with a village in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref50; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 13.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Deserts; Landscapes; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Palestine
  - Two men working in a tannery in Hebron, with Al-Haram al-Ibrahimi/Cave of the Patriarchs in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref51; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Animals; Men; Group Portraits; Workers; Cave of the Patriarchs/Cave of Machpelah/Al-Haram al-Ibrahimi; Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Sites; Hebron/Al-Khalil; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Palestine
  - A landscape of Khirbet Qana (Mamshit)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref52; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 14.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Nazareth; Religious Sites; Landscapes; Palestine
  - Terraced slopes of Wadi Neow near Artuf, Palestine., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref53; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Artuf; Outdoors; Palestine; Landscapes
  - A person standing in front of mosque on Mount of Olives, Palestine., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref54; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Mosques; Religious Sites; Men; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Palestine
  - A mountain and a lake., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref55; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 9.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Water; Lakes; Palestine; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Boats/Ships; Transportation
  - The ruins of a stone structure., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref56; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Deserts; Mountains/Hills; Palestine; Landscapes; Photographic Prints
  - A landscape of a building on top of a mountain surrounded by trees (link ref60)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref57; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 13 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Buildings; Forest/Woodlands; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - A landscape of woodlands., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref58; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 11.7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Forest/Woodlands; Mountains/Hills; Water; Landscapes; Palestine; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A train crossing a bridge over a river with mountains in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref59; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 x 9.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Trains; Railways; Transportation; Water; Bridges; Mountains/Hills; Forest/Woodlands; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - A landscape of a building on top of a mountain surrounded by trees (link ref57)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref60; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 12.8cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Landscapes; Buildings; Forest/Woodlands; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - The Tomb of the Kings with a building in the background, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref61; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Sites; Jerusalem; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; English Writing; Palestine
  - An aerial view of a village., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref62; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Buildings; Palestine; Architecture; Water; Palm Trees; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Landscapes
  - People on a hillside with animals., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref63; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Camels; Donkeys; Goats; Animals; Men; Children; Boys; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - A man on a horse in front of a stone building., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref64; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Regional/National Dress; Horses; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - The Tomb of Jacob within Al-Haram al-Ibrahimi/Cave of the Patriarchs, Hebron., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref65; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 7.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Arabic Calligraphy; Cave of the Patriarchs/Cave of Machpelah/Al-Haram al-Ibrahimi; Tombs/Mausoleums; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Gelatin Silver Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Hebron/Al-Khalil; English Writing; Books; Furnishings; Palestine; Quran/Koran; Lanterns/Lamps
  - Nasri Fuleihan sitting in front of Wadi Zarqa Ma'in, Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref66; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Outdoors; Men; Hats; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Ma'in, Jordan
  - Amdursky's Hotel and the Banco di Roma on Armenian Patriarchate Street, taken from the Tower of David., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref67; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 13.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Signs/Signposts; Advertisements; Hotels; Banks; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Streets/Roads; Jerusalem; English Writing; Carriages/Coaches; Crowds; Animals; Transportation; Buildings; Restaurants/bars; Religious Sites; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; English Writing; Palestine; Landscapes
  - People on a shoreline with buildings in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref68; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 13.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Coast; Water; Men; Women; Buildings; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes
  - Two men standing on a cliffside., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref69; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Men; Group Portraits; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A man riding a horse with tents in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref70; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 13.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Horses; Animals; Men; Individual Portraits; Tents; Deserts; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Regional/National Dress; Embroidery; Palestine
  - People in front of the Damascus gate in Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref71; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 13.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Jerusalem; Damascus Gate, Jerusalem; Doors/Entrances; Religious Sites; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Streets/Roads
  - People on a shoreline with buildings in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref72; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Water; Men; Women; Architecture; Buildings; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes
  - The Dome of the Rock with the Mount of Olives and Russian Church in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref73; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Churches; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Landscapes; English Writing; Palestine
  - Exterior of the Garden tomb., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref75; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints; Jerusalem; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; English Writing; Palestine
  - Women standing near a herd of animals., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref76; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Goats; Donkeys; Sheep; Camels; Animals; Antelopes; Photographic Prints; Deserts; Agriculture/Farms; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Women; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of men in front of a tents (linked ref201)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref77; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Tents; Men; Group Portraits; Palestine; Regional/National Dress; Uniforms; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Boys; Children; Deserts; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Military/Soldiers; Turbans
  - A mountainous landscape., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref78; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - Men on horses in front of a mountain., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref79; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Group Portraits; Horses; Animals; Mountains/Hills; Deserts; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes
  - A man posing beside a campfire., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref80; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 12.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Hats; Guns; Weapons; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Palestine
  - View of the village Bayt Nattif., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref81; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Buildings; Architecture; Palestine; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Bayt Nattif
  - A woman standing in front of a coloumn in the Temple Mount, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref82; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Jerusalem; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Individual Portraits; Umbrellas/Parasols; Palestine
  - View from rooftop of Simon the Tanner's home, Jaffa., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref84; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Boats/Ships; Transportation; Coast; Water; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Jaffa; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Palestine
  - Horses and men in front of tent with Ottoman flags., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref85; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 14.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Tents; Flags; Mountains/Hills; Horses; Animals; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - A mountainous landscape., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref86; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Two men posing in underwear and hats., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref87; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11 x 8.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Hats; Men; Cigarettes; Smoking; Group Portraits; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - Greek orthodox clergymen standing in front of the Church of the Holy Sepulchre., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref88; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 1.4 x 8.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Buildings; Priests/Clergymen; Hats; Orthodox Christianity; Photographic Prints; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Palestine; English Writing; Jerusalem; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Churches; Religious Sites
  - Man kneeling in front of Grotto of the Agony, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref89; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Religious Sites; Priests/Clergymen; Religious Crosses; Furnishings; Lanterns/Lamps; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Individual Portraits; Praying; English Writing; Palestine
  - Interior of the Cathedral of Saint James, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref90; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Churches; Religious Sites; Chandeliers; Architecture; Religious Crosses; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Furnishings; English Writing; Palestine
  - Camel tracks on sand., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref91; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.5 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Animals; Deserts; Camels; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; English Writing
  - Badland formations in Kerak, Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref92; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Kerak, Jordan; Water; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; English Writing
  - Priest inside of Adam's Chapel and Adam's tomb, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref93; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Furnishings; Chandeliers; Religious Crosses; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Individual Portraits; Facial Hair; Religious Sites; Tombs/Mausoleums; Jerusalem; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Churches; English Writing; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A mountainous landscape., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref94; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Deserts; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - Person entering the Church of Nativity., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref95; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Individual Portraits; Religious Sites; Church of the Nativity; Churches; Bethlehem; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - The Cyclopean Wall, Baalbek., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref96; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 7.9 com (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)